What are you doing here?
What a coincidence, Ms. Liang.
What's wrong?
Is it about my brother again?
Why don't you reconsider me?
Get lost.
Ms. Liang,
it'd be a shame if you hurt your hand.
Drinks are on me tonight for Ms. Liang.
My treat.
I don't need you.
I can pay for my own drinks.
Get lost.
He Yu.
It tickles.
Why are you tickling me?
Stop. Stop tickling me.
Stop it.
Mrs. He,
this is an eel.
It can prevent athlete's foot.
Take it away.
I specially sent someone
to buy it this morning.
Mrs. He,
it's so slippery.
Take it away.
Then... I'll take it away.
Take it away. Hurry.
Take it away.
Mrs. He,
eels are very nutritious.
Don't make me slap you.
If you won't eat it, I will.
Bring it back.
Where is He Shi?
He Shi hasn't been back all night.
Help!
I'll beat you to death,
you little brat! Dad!
I'll beat you to death!
Beat you to death!
I was wrong.
Brother Liang.
Dad.
What's going on?
Mr. He,
I'm marrying my daughter
to your second son,
not to be his concubine.
What is the meaning of this?
You tell them.
She... She was drunk
and mistook me for He Yu.
Bullshit!
You clearly drugged me.
Good thing I woke up in time.
Dad!
You animal!
Did you think I didn't know
about your usual affairs?
How dare you touch Ms. Liang!
Dad, I was wrong! Dad!
He Shi is the CEO of He Group.
This is truly disgraceful.
The whip.
Li Zhangxin, you...
Stop hitting He Shi.
Shu Roujing, you...
Dad!
You animal!
How dare you embarrass me out there!
Dad!
I'll beat you to death!
Dad! You animal!
Stop hitting him.
Stop it.
Dad, stop it.
You bastard.
Stop it.
You'll cripple him.
You bastard!
From today on,
you are no longer the CEO of He Group.
Dad, please don't!
No.
Then what about my daughter?
Her engagement party with He Yu
will proceed as planned.
I don't agree.
Whoever dares to disobey me again
can get out
of here.
Roujing,
I'm here to apply your medicine.
Honey,
you're the best.
You're the only one who came to see me.
Hubby,
you really dare to sleep with anyone, huh?
I...
She seduced me.
What kind of medicine is this?
It hurts so much.
It's to reduce the inflammation.
Salt?
Shu Roujing!
Hubby,
bear with it.
I'm doing this for your own good.
It breaks my heart too.
Honey,
I was wrong.
Second Brother,
where are you going?
Since Dad is so firm on this,
I'll just leave the He family.
Aren't you playing right into
Zhang Xin and He Shi's hands?
Zhangxin,
if I can't be with you,
I'd rather never get married.
But if you leave,
who will protect me in this house?
Let me talk to Dad again, okay?
Come in.
Have some Fu tea
to lower your blood pressure.
I know you're worried about
what happened to the eldest brother.
But the second brother shouldn't bear
the consequences of his mistakes.
I hope you don't make a rash decision.
Recite the He family rules
to me again.
The family rules echo with lasting charm.
The earnest advice in the hall lingers on.
Parents' love and children's filial piety
weave a net of affection.
Brothers respect each other
like flying geese.
Elders are as steady and secure
as pine trees.
A kind word warms the heart.
In the He family, my word is law.
The reason our family
has prospered until now
is because of unity and mutual help.
As He Shi's younger brother,
He Yu
ought to fulfill
his brother's obligations.
But if our hearts aren't together,
what's the point of
the He family's existence?
I went through so much trouble
to bring you back,
not to have you lecture me.
Dad,
do you really care about Mom and me?
Then why do you still keep Zhang Xin
in the He family
when you know she harmed us?
For all these years,
if Zhang Xin hadn't been managing
the He family,
it would have been a mess long ago.
Now you want me to kick her out?
How would the outside world
judge us?
As expected,
the He family's reputation is
the most important thing to you.
Anyone can be a sacrifice.
Madam,
would you like anything to eat tonight?
That's 150 GB.
Thank goodness,
they're all here.
I'm still as charming as ever.
I look pretty good
from this angle.
Exciting, baby?
You're even wilder than me.
He Shi,
dressed like this,
am I prettier than all the maids?